{
    "id": "cf92ffe5792c42939182bbb78ba15541",
    "title": "Adverbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Don’t speak loudly. We are in the church.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "speak",
                "loudly",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "118ede2a97574650b550fbd6347f5b57"
        },
        {
            "question": "Can I come tomorrow?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "come",
                "tomorrow"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1f2031fdfc2a4decbb6e6783f00b30f6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Are you busy now?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are",
                "busy",
                "now"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "99196c0d097f4818af954b056fd55e43"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t worry. You will hear from us soon.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "worry",
                "will",
                "from",
                "soon"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "edec55f38f5349febfa0cbf5cb913729"
        },
        {
            "question": "Listen carefully to what I say.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "listen",
                "carefully",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f1e2ecd5f929406c845beaa46ba1810f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The sun is shining brightly.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sun",
                "shining",
                "brightly"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2d9163816d5446128fbc5bf857b6c6e1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I had a strange experience yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "had",
                "strange",
                "yesterday"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f4cf212c357740c19c055a15c67a8716"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wanted to talk to her but she hastily left the room.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "talk",
                "her",
                "hastily",
                "left"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "75813abfa2ff4a248fe474b6390e562e"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is standing outside.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "standing",
                "outside"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2370f979bbc34becb331a65caa95f175"
        },
        {
            "question": "This has been going on for a while.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "been",
                "going",
                "for",
                "while"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "4fdfe0ff1a6c4283838993b3c39b3c5d"
        }
    ]
}